Tufts Weekly UP056
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 February 27; UP056.001.027.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.04 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 March 05; UP056.001.027.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.29 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 March 12; UP056.001.027.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 16.75 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 March 19; UP056.001.027.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.78 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 March 26; UP056.001.027.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.00 Megabytes (Box 27)
    [All Around Club] Fashion Show (incl. photos).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 April 09; UP056.001.027.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.50 Megabytes (Box 27)
    Lester R. Adelson, 1935
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 April 16; UP056.001.027.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.43 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 April 23; UP056.001.027.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 22.04 Megabytes (Box 27)
    [All Around Club] Hanry Cabot Lodge, Jr. is speaker. Tufts Weekly Pictoral Supplement.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 April 30; UP056.001.027.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.09 Megabytes (Box 27)
    [All Around Club] Hanry Cabot Lodge, Jr. is speaker.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 May 07; UP056.001.027.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.30 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 May 14; UP056.001.027.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.71 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 May 21; UP056.001.027.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.56 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 May 28; UP056.001.027.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.66 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 June 18; UP056.001.027.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.54 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 September 24; UP056.001.028.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 October 01; UP056.001.028.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 October 08; UP056.001.028.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 October 15; UP056.001.028.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 October 22; UP056.001.028.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 October 29; UP056.001.028.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 November 05; UP056.001.028.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 November 12; UP056.001.028.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 November 19; UP056.001.028.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 November 26; UP056.001.028.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 December 03; UP056.001.028.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
    [Alumni council] Art fund established
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 December 10; UP056.001.028.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Sorority Formal.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1936 December 17; UP056.001.028.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
    Alumni relatives among undergraduates
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 January 07; UP056.001.028.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 January 14; UP056.001.028.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 February 11; UP056.001.028.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 28)
    [Alumnae Hall] Kaye MacKinnon gives dance recital for benefit of Alumnae Hall; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 February 18; UP056.001.028.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 February 25; UP056.001.028.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 March 04; UP056.001.028.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
    All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega entertain fifteen children in "Big Brother Movement".
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 March 11; UP056.001.028.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 March 18; UP056.001.028.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 March 25; UP056.001.028.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 April 01; UP056.001.028.00023 (Box 28)
    April Fool Issue.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 April 08; UP056.001.028.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 April 15; UP056.001.028.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 April 23; UP056.001.028.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 28)
    American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 April 29; UP056.001.028.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 May 06; UP056.001.028.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 May 13; UP056.001.028.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 May 20; UP056.001.028.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 May 27; UP056.001.028.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Sorority formal, senior party.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 June 15; UP056.001.028.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 September 23; UP056.001.029.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 September 30; UP056.001.029.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
    President Cousins Memorial Issue.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 October 07; UP056.001.029.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
    Alpha Kappa Pi. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 October 15; UP056.001.029.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 October 21; UP056.001.029.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 October 28; UP056.001.029.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
    Academic Honors p. 1; Alumni council
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 November 04; UP056.001.029.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
    Alpha Tau Omega members isolated because of diptheria quarantine
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 November 12; UP056.001.029.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 November 18; UP056.001.029.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 November 24; UP056.001.029.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 December 02; UP056.001.029.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 December 09; UP056.001.029.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1937 December 16; UP056.001.029.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
    Roy Akagi speaker at Fletcher Scool on the Far East. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 January 06; UP056.001.029.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 January 13; UP056.001.029.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 January 20; UP056.001.029.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 February 10; UP056.001.029.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
    Louis Abdu (A 1938, M 1942). Photo.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 February 17; UP056.001.029.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 February 25; UP056.001.029.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 March 03; UP056.001.029.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 March 10; UP056.001.029.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 March 17; UP056.001.029.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
    John Adams. Elected captain of Track for 1938-39.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 March 24; UP056.001.029.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 April 07; UP056.001.029.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 29)
    [All Aound Club] Elections and Activities. Alpha Kappa Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 April 14; UP056.001.029.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 April 21; UP056.001.029.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
    [All Aound Club] Elections and Activities.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 April 28; UP056.001.029.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 May 06; UP056.001.029.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 May 12; UP056.001.029.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 May 19; UP056.001.029.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 May 26; UP056.001.029.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 June 14; UP056.001.029.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 October 01; UP056.001.030.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 October 06; UP056.001.030.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 October 13; UP056.001.030.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 October 20; UP056.001.030.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 30)
    Academic Honors. (Incl. photos - James G. Weldon and Persis Proctor) pp. 1, 2
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 October 27; UP056.001.030.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 November 03; UP056.001.030.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 30)
    [Alumni council] Gift of college mace to President Carmichael [includes photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 November 10; UP056.001.030.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
    [All Around Club] Elections and Activites.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 November 17; UP056.001.030.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 November 25; UP056.001.030.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 December 01; UP056.001.030.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 December 08; UP056.001.030.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1938 December 15; UP056.001.030.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 January 13; UP056.001.030.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 January 19; UP056.001.030.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 February 09; UP056.001.030.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 February 16; UP056.001.030.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 February 24; UP056.001.030.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
    Alpha Kappa Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 March 02; UP056.001.030.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 March 09; UP056.001.030.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 March 16; UP056.001.030.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 March 23; UP056.001.030.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 April 06; UP056.001.030.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 April 13; UP056.001.030.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 April 21; UP056.001.030.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 April 28; UP056.001.030.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 May 04; UP056.001.030.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 May 11; UP056.001.030.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 May 18; UP056.001.030.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 May 25; UP056.001.030.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 June 02; UP056.001.030.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 June 20; UP056.001.030.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
    Commencement Issue; Alumni council
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 September 28; UP056.001.031.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 October 05; UP056.001.031.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 October 13; UP056.001.031.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 October 19; UP056.001.031.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
    Academic Honors. p. 1, 4
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 October 26; UP056.001.031.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 November 02; UP056.001.031.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Xi Delta; Alumni council; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 November 09; UP056.001.031.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 November 16; UP056.001.031.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
    Alpha Omicron Pi; Alumni win awards at Columbia University School of Medicine
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 November 23; UP056.001.031.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 November 30; UP056.001.031.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 December 07; UP056.001.031.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club. Alpha Xi Delta. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1939 December 14; UP056.001.031.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 January 11; UP056.001.031.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 January 18; UP056.001.031.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 February 08; UP056.001.031.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 February 15; UP056.001.031.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 February 23; UP056.001.031.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 February 29; UP056.001.031.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 March 07; UP056.001.031.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 March 14; UP056.001.031.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 March 21; UP056.001.031.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 April 03; UP056.001.031.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 April 11; UP056.001.031.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club (incl. photo- Florence Towle). Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 April 18; UP056.001.031.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 31)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 April 25; UP056.001.031.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 31)
    Alpha Xi Delta [photo of Marion Savage]. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 May 09; UP056.001.031.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 May 16; UP056.001.031.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 May 23; UP056.001.031.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 May 31; UP056.001.031.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 June 18; UP056.001.031.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 September 27; UP056.001.032.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 October 03; UP056.001.032.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 October 10; UP056.001.032.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 October 17; UP056.001.032.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 October 24; UP056.001.032.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 October 31; UP056.001.032.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 November 07; UP056.001.032.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Academic Honors. pp. 1, 3
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 November 15; UP056.001.032.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 November 21; UP056.001.032.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Freeland K. Abbott. (faculty), Review of "Confessions of an Individualist" by W.H. Chamberlin, p. 2.; Academic Honors p. 2 (ed)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 November 29; UP056.001.032.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 32)
    New Chapter Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 December 05; UP056.001.032.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Freeland K. Abbott. (faculty), Review of "Confessions of an Individualist" by W.H. Chamberlin, p. 2.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 December 12; UP056.001.032.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1940 December 19; UP056.001.032.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    New Chapter Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 January 09; UP056.001.032.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 January 16; UP056.001.032.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 February 06; UP056.001.032.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 February 13; UP056.001.032.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). Alpha Tau Omega. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 February 20; UP056.001.032.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alpha Xi Delta. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Epsilon Pi New Chapter. Freeland K. Abbott. Comments on speech by William Y. Elliott.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 February 27; UP056.001.032.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 March 06; UP056.001.032.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 March 13; UP056.001.032.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi New Chapter. Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 March 20; UP056.001.032.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 March 27; UP056.001.032.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alpha Xi Delta. Alpha Epsilon Pi New Chapter. Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 April 01; UP056.001.032.00024 (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 April 10; UP056.001.032.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 32)
    [All Around Club] Activities.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 April 16; UP056.001.032.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Epsilon Pi New Chapter. Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 April 24; UP056.001.032.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 32)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 May 01; UP056.001.032.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Tau Omega, dedicate main room to memory of Frank G. Wren
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 May 08; UP056.001.032.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alpha Tau Omega dedicate room to memory of Frank G. Wren; Alpha Omicron Pi. Academic Honors. pp. 1, 6 (incl. photos - Carol Barker and Eddie Dugger). Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club).
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 May 15; UP056.001.032.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 May 22; UP056.001.032.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 32)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 May 29; UP056.001.032.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    New Chapter Alpha Epsilon Pi; Alpha Kappa Pi; Alpha Omicron Pi; Alpha Tau Omega; Alumni day
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 June 16; UP056.001.032.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 September 26; UP056.001.033.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1941-1942. Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 October 02; UP056.001.033.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Tau Omega. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 October 09; UP056.001.033.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi 1941-1942. Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Kappa Pi; [Alumnae Hall] projects to raise funds for Alumnae Hall
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 October 17; UP056.001.033.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Academic Honors. pp. 1, 4
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 October 23; UP056.001.033.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 33)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 October 30; UP056.001.033.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 33)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 November 06; UP056.001.033.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Suspended from interfraternity competition for infraction of rushing rules.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 November 14; UP056.001.033.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 November 21; UP056.001.033.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 33)
    [Alumnae Hall] projects to raise funds for Alumnae Hall; Alpha Xi Delta. [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Epsilon Pi 1941-1942. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 November 27; UP056.001.033.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 December 11; UP056.001.033.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 December 04; UP056.001.033.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 33)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1941 December 18; UP056.001.033.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alexander Bain Society.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1942 January 08; UP056.001.033.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1942 January 15; UP056.001.033.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1942 January 29; UP056.001.033.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Tau Omega. Alpha Xi Delta. [American institute for chemical engineers] Tufts society granted charter
  - Tufts Weekly, 1942 February 05; UP056.001.033.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1942 February 12; UP056.001.033.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Xi Delta. Alpha Omicron Pi. [All Around Club] Activities. [Administration] Objection to ruling on term grades. p. 3. Alpha Kappa Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1942 February 19; UP056.001.033.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 33)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.